- [Voiceover] Mystery Science
Theater 3000, show 512.
Reel one.
♫ In the not-too-distant future
♫ Next Sunday, A.D.
♫ There was a guy named Joel
♫ Not too different from you or me
♫ He worked at Gizmonic Institute
♫ Just another face in a red jumpsuit
♫ He did a good job cleaning up the place
♫ But his bosses didn't like him
♫ So they shot him into space
♫ We'll send him cheesy movies
♫ The worst we can find, la la la
♫ He'll have to sit and watch them all
♫ And we'll monitor his mind, la la la
♫ Now keep in mind Joel can't control
♫ Where the movies begin or end, la la la
♫ Because he used those special parts
♫ To make his robot friends
♫ Robot roll call
♫ Cambot
♫ Gypsy, hi girl
♫ Tom Servo, what a cool guy
♫ Crow
♫ If you're wondering
how he eats and breathes
♫ And other science facts, la la la
♫ Then repeat to yourself it's just a show
♫ I should really just relax
♫ For Mystery Science Theater 3000 ♫
- Hi everybody.
Welcome to the Satellite of Love.
I'm Joel Robinson.
Oh, look here comes Tom
Servo, Crow T. robot.
- Hello.
- [Tom] Evening.
- Hey come on up here you guys.
I wanna show you this toothpick sculpture
I've been workin' on for
the last three years.
- You been workin' three years on that?
- Well yeah, nights and weekends.
- Not every good.
- [Tom] Shh.
- I mean, what is it?
- It's a scale reproduction model of
Monticello rendered in toothpick.
I got the idea off the nickel, see?
- It's beautiful.
- Where'd you get all the toothpicks?
- What are you kidding?
We're on a spaceship.
This place is crawling with toothpicks.
- Well, it really is cool Joel.
Of course, you know
we'll have to break it.
- It's nothing personal, you understand.
It's just a thing we have to do.
- Yeah.
- [Joel] Okay.
- [Robots] Huh?
- Sure, go ahead, that's
why I made it, smash away.
- No, no, no Joel.
You're ruining it for me.
- Yeah, I feel dirty.
- [Voiceover] Commercial
sign in five seconds.
- Sure seems like a waste,
it being all toothpicky
and fragile and all.
- [Voiceover] Commercial sign now.
- I'm just gonna leave it here
unattended
to dry.
We'll be right back.
(robots screaming)
("Love Theme from MST3K")
- [Joel] So how was it for you?
- Well, as far as breaking stuff goes,
it was good, not great.
- Yeah, not as good as that
ceramic bell collection.
- Oh, Mellowitz and
Associates are calling.
- Okay and this?
- Oh, let me see.
Oh, (laughing) that's my old head.
Just file that under
"Frank's first head", okay?
- [Mike] Right.
- Oh, hi, Joel.
Look we're way too busy to
even do an invention this week.
We're being audited.
You go right ahead though.
- It's a Daktari stool!
- What do you think, sirs?
- Daktari stool?
Whatever.
Anyway, Joel, it's a madhouse down here.
We're being audited by the
Fraternal Order of Mad Science.
You know, one of those,
"Are-you-really-mad-enough?"
sort of things.
- Frank, three Jarvik sevens.
- Put 'em in the junk drawer, Jeez.
Didn't the temp agency test
you on any of this stuff?
- Well, I'm a little off my game.
I'm not normally required
to wear leg iron like this.
Say what is the deal with this
guy and those cute robots?
- Listen, Mr.
Four-dollars-and-25-cents-an-hour.
You stick with the boxes, and
I'll handle the experiment.
Is that all right with you?
- Frank, can I see you a minute?
- Sure thing, Doctor F.
Say, Steve, this temp
stuff is workin' out great,
don't you think?
- [Steve] I'm so glad your
little friend is working
out so nicely, Frank.
Now, what about sending
Joel the movie, you boob?
- The movie, the movie, the movie.
- Oh, for the love of.
- [Frank] The movie, movie,
(Frank talking to himself)
- Oh, Frank, look remember?
The double butt graft, my
science project from Evil-O's.
I grafted the butt of a
dog onto the butt of a cat.
Sure they all laughed.
- Dr. F., the movie, the movie.
- Oh, right.
Here it is, "Mitchell,"
starring Joe Don Baker.
- You guys watch Joe Don Baker movies?
- Oh, look just get
back to work, temp boy.
- Well, here it comes, Joel.
"Mitchell," it's a super secret spy,
has a
motorcycle-marooned-in-space-meets-Hercules
or
not.
Watch it and weep, Joel, pro mole.
Send him the movie, Frank.
Frank, the movie.
(Joel talking)
(shouting all at once)
- [All] Oh my God, movie time!
- [Crow] Hey, look, a sex film.
- [Tom] Mittens?
An action film called "Mittens?"
- [Crow] Joe Don Baker
is Mittens, he's a cop.
- [Tom] Or is it Mithril?
Oh wait, it's "Mitchell."
- [Crow] Oh, the Martha Mitchell Story.
- [Tom] Joe Don Baker is
Martha Mitchell. (laughing)
(exciting music)
- [Crow] It's Bigfoot!
- [Tom] Who's the puffy guy
who's the big lurid sex machine?
- [Robots] Mitchell!
- [Tom] That Mitchell is one fat--
- [Crow] Shut your mouth!
- [Tom] I'm just talking about Mitchell.
- [Crow] Looks like Grendel.
- [Joel] Hey, Linda Evans!
That was her pre-Yanni days.
- [Tom] Before her face was pulled taut.
- [Joel] Looks kind of
like a slow motion sneeze?
(laughing)
- [Crow] Yeah, here's
your loser actor bouquet.
- [Tom] Any movie with "waka
jo waka" is okay by me.
(mimicking music)
♫ It was the third of September
♫ A day I'll always remember ♫
- [Crow] Never corner a
Mitchell, see how he reacts.
- [Joel] Looks like he's doing a Nixon.
- [Tom] Looks like a middle-aged Chucky.
- [Crow] He looks like a wrathful Buddha.
- [Tom] He looks like the
moon in "A Trip to the Moon."
- [Joel] Man, I can't get my arms down.
(laughing)
- [Crow] And now he looks
like a small-mouthed bass.
- [Tom] Now he looks like
he's in a wind tunnel!
- [Joel] Now um,
(mimicking music)
maybe he's doing tai chi or something.
- [Crow] Mitchell's on the corner.
- [All] Mitchell!
- [Tom] Eegah.
Shtemlo.
- [Joel] Watch out for snakes!
- [Tom] We've hidden Mitchell
somewhere in this picture.
- [Crow] Mitchell, will
you stand up please?
♫ The lunatic is on the grass ♫
(laughing)
- [Tom] Johnny Nash breaks
into a suburban home.
Mitchell.
- [Joel] Hey, it's one
of the kids from "Fame."
- [Tom] Which one?
- [Joel] Any of them.
- [Crow] Johnny Mathis!
♫ It's not for me to say ♫
- [Tom] The Green Hornet.
- This little thing, she
can't be more than 16.
Every time she gives me a manicure,
she tells me she's having
a different affair.
And she tells me everything.
I mean all the real hot and juicy details.
I can't even keep my fingers still.
- [Crow] Must be a faculty meeting.
- I'm thinking.
(glass breaking)
- [Joel] Uh, it's open.
- [Crow] It's like he's
breaking out of his house.
- [Joel] Al Noga?
- [Tom] No, still Johnny Mathis.
- [Joel] Oh.
- [Crow] Oh, yeah, close it and lock it,
you don't want anyone coming in.
- [Joel] Doctor Detroit.
With songs by Devo, Cutting
Crew, and Haircut 100.
♫ I say to myself it's wonderful ♫
- [Joel] A picture of Mo Connolly?
- [Tom] No, not the limited edition
Star Trek collector plates!
- [Joel] Hey, Lucas McCain lives here.
- [Tom] They're on a
collision course to wackiness!
(laughing)
Alright, last call, drink 'em up.
- [Crow] Let's not talk.
(woman laughing)
- [Joel] Hey, oh a Goldstar.
- [Tom] Move it along, please.
Should I tell her?
- Ladies, you know where everything is.
I want you to exercise
the bottomless resources
of your imaginations.
- [Joel] Uh, can I have a lamp?
- Surprise me.
The way you always do.
Come on, Don, let's get some juice.
- [Crow] Fresh panties, all around.
- [Joel] Might be able to
kiss her tonight, you know.
- Who the hell does he
think I am, an acrobat?
- [Crow] And she's an acrobat, Ted!
- [Tom] Santa?
Wait a minute, I think maybe
the Snoop Sisters are in there.
- [Crow] I'm gonna get a
series before Stuart Margolin.
- [Joel] Shh.
- [Tom] Johnny Mathis?
Alright, get my gun!
- [Joel] Well, you know,
it’s not often you see
Johnny Mathis in the wild.
- [Tom] Need some clean underwear.
Hmm, one of these.
- [Crow] Hey, a Gunderoo.
- [Joel] Don't shoot me, the burglar!
- [Crow] So are we gonna play bridge?
- We got another patient on it.
- No, wait.
(men whispering)
Shh.
- [Joel] Uh hello, this
is Carlton your doorman.
- [Crow] Cedar lattice, works every time.
- [Tom] Chances are, huh?
- [Joel] If that’s John Saxon, I’m dead.
- [Tom] Sonny, are we like bait?
- [Crow] We're closed!
Maybe I should get back to work.
- Hey!
- [Joel] What?
(gunfire)
Oh!
- [Tom] Meanwhile, on an
"Adam-12" episode not far away.
(voice on police radio)
- [Voiceover] A possible TB
at 1020 Maple Land Drive.
Investigate--
- [Joel] Our hero, ladies
and gentlemen, right there.
- 22, can you get me a
picture of Maple Land Drive,
is it off Beverly Glen?
- [Voiceover] This is 22, you've got it,
it's one block east.
- Alright.
(police siren)
- [Crow] Uh, just five more minutes.
- [Tom] Mitchell honey, we're
home, put your shoes on.
- [Police Officer] Private
enterprise beat us to it, huh?
- [Joel] Hello, public sector!
- Hey what do you say, Jimmy?
- Hello Tom.
Where's the body?
- In the den.
- [Tom] We posed him.
- Think you're gonna
need us around here?
- Nah, that's okay, thanks.
- We'll take off then, it's all yours.
- Sure.
- [Crow] Ah, rent a
cops, private enterprise,
why don't you go back to the mall!
- Hey, you coming Mitchell?
- Yeah.
- [Tom] Got any moist
towelettes, rags, toilet paper?
- [Joel] Come on, Mr. Two
Years from "Eischied," come on.
(man talking quickly)
- If I find one of those wetbacks--
- [Joel And Robots] Hey!
- Wall full of guns for my gun rack,
unfortunately I got another gun sooner.
- [Joel] Oh, smart.
(man speaking quickly)
- I had no choice, I had to shoot him.
- [Crow] Well, you're rich and white,
I don't see a problem with it.
- [Police Officer] A pretty clean job.
- [Joel] Come on, it's fun!
- [Tom] You got a sofa I could
stretch out on for a little while?
- [Crow] Oh, there's the body.
- [Joel] Hey, here, watch what happens
when I step on his abdomen.
(slurping sound)
- [Tom] I think he's gonna need
a bigger body bag than that.
- [Mitchell] All those guns loaded?
- Some of them.
Not always sure which.
- [Crow] They're randomly loaded.
It's a little game I play.
- [Tom] All your guests loaded?
(suspenseful music)
- The guests are leaving.
- Party's over.
♫ Time to call it a day ♫
- Anybody tell them they could leave?
- I did.
- There's a police
investigation going on here.
- [Joel] Oh there is?
I thought there was just a big
slob walking around my house.
- [Crow] Where's the john?
I'm gonna flush this.
- My guests have to be at a
desk at eight in the morning.
He's an important person.
My secretary will give you
their names and addresses.
- [Tom] And disavow any
knowledge of their actions.
- [Joel] Man, he's good.
- [Tom] Mitchell, pardon me, Mitchell.
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Hey, can I have a scotch?
- What's your name?
- Mitchell.
- [Tom] Why?
- [Mitchell] What's yours?
- Well find him, wherever he is.
(man talking quickly)
- [Joel] Oh, he's talking
to Commissioner Gordon.
- Get ahold of Mistretta.
Tell him to talk to Gallano.
- [Tom] Okay, sleeve length 34,
36 in down seam, and a 32 in inseam.
- [Crow] Orson Bean, he's a cop!
- [Tom] I told Mistretta
to talk to Gallano.
I think.
- [Joel] What?
("Love Theme from MST3K")
- Mitchell.
- [Joel] What?
- People don't like you.
In fact I don't care for you myself.
Why is that?
- [Crow] Perhaps our
brief but bitter affair?
- You refuse to sign this report, why?
- [Joel] Yeah, I'm still
on the first question.
- What kind of a policeman are you anyway?
What are you gonna do,
file a separate report?
- I don't know.
- What do you know?
- [Joel] Uh, I don't know.
- None of Deaney's other guns were loaded.
Now the collection is
way up high on the wall.
The burglar, he looks to
be only five four is all.
- So, what does that prove?
- That Deaney's lying and he's
not gonna get away with it.
- [Crow] Oh, I'll come over there!
- You're gonna get me mad, Mitchell,
and when that happens, I wouldn't
want to be in your shoes.
Now get out there.
- [Joel] Mitchell's the sensible cop.
- See Aldridge.
He's got an assignment for you.
And remember, don't you
dare go near Deaney.
You forget about him.
- [Tom] They arrested Harlan Ellison!
- [Joel] Good.
- [Aldridge] Come in
Mitchell, take a seat.
- [Crow] Mom said no, huh?
So you come to me, the nice cop.
- [Joel] Wow, he sounds and
smells like William Conrad.
- Chief Pallin has ordered
the surveillance of a man
called James Arthur Cummings.
- James Arthur Cummings?
- [Aldridge] Yeah, you heard of him?
- No.
- 24 hour surveillance, and
I want you to stay with him
so A, you bug him enough that he cracks
or B, he comes up with
some kind of statement
or incriminates himself
concerning a crime in Mexico.
- [Crow] Or C,
- [Mitchell] Okay.
- [Crow] you get drunk and pass out again.
- Who do I get?
- You get nobody.
- Huh?
- Nobody.
- What do I do for sleeping?
How 'bout eating?
- Nothing's gonna happen
in the middle of the night.
- Oh.
- [Tom] But I wanna eat!
- You get six hours shuteye
from midnight to six AM.
- [Tom] But eating!
- Now Mitchell, those are Pallin's orders.
You want to call him?
See Tyzack, he'll take
you to Cummings' place.
- Import, export of stolen merchandise,
that is Cummings' big scene.
This week it's a big heroin
hijack, it comes out of Mexico,
a kilo, full kilo,
that's two million bucks.
It may be Pallin's idea of a joke,
but leaning on Cummings
is no joke, my friend,
no one leans on Cummings,
because he stamps on people,
and he's got a big shoe.
- Let me ask you something.
- [Tom] Who are you?
- If Pallin gave you this
job leaning on Cummings,
would you say he's given
you a good assignment?
- [Joel] Oh, don't suck honey.
- I'd say that he was quietly
shipping you out of the way.
- I'll get 'em both, Deaney and Cummings.
- No way.
You don't get neither.
- That's what Pallin thinks, right?
- Right.
- Wrong.
- [Tom] Excuse me, I
don't feel good at all.
- [Joel] Hey man, thanks
for driving me to my car,
nice to have it pre-parked
at the stakeout, see ya!
♫ Don't be discouraged, the man don't ♫
- [Crow] Whoa, don't do that!
Oh, phew.
Mitchell!
- [Joel] Andy Capp?
- [Tom] Boy, Flo’s really
gonna be mad, I’m drunk again.
(Crow breathing heavily)
- [Mitchell] Cummings!
- [Tom] Stop or my heart will explode!
Cummings!
Uh, Mitchell, police department.
- That's not due til January, son.
- Uh, Mr. Cummings.
- Make an appointment, son,
have your chief give me a ring.
- Mr. Cummings.
- No salesmen at this entrance.
- [Tom] But I'm not a salesman,
I'm the chubby blue line!
- [Crow] As an actor,
Merlin Olsen hadn’t
found his instrument yet.
(Tom breathing heavily)
(sad music)
- [Crow] Whoa, that thing with the deal-o.
- [Joel] Oh, think there's a potato cake
in here or something.
- [Tom] He seems down, I’ll
send him a Pick Me Up Bouquet.
- [Crow] Somewhere, an Indian is crying.
- [Joel] I’m gonna call Lady Bird Johnson.
(Crow snoring)
- [Tom] Fluffernutter!
- Alright now, what do you want?
- I've got some questions.
- No questions.
- What do you know about
a man named Mistretta
and some heroin hijack down in Mexico?
- Heroin?
- Yeah, Cuernavaca, Mexico, about a kilo,
so you know a truck,
ambushed, hijacked, you know.
- Look, Mitchell.
- [Tom] I'm King Hussein.
- This is Los Angeles, California,
I don't know anything about heroin
or someone's got his wires crossed.
- Oh.
- [Joel] We're not in New York?
- Well I've been told to
watch you, Mr. Cummings,
so I guess that's what I'm gonna do.
- Can I give you some advice, son?
- Yes sir.
- Watch out for falling rocks.
- [Tom] Oh, okay.
Say, you got any burgers
or something in there?
- [Joel] Man, I'm constantly confused.
- [Tom] Watch out for falling rocks, huh?
Stupid.
- [Voiceover] And that
was the midnight edition
of the news on KKRO.
- [Crow] Hey, Crow Radio!
- [Joel] Goodnight, John-Boy.
- [Tom] Falling rocks,
I just don't get it.
- [Joel] Lights, your lights!
- [Tom] I miss him.
- [Joel] Well, almost
time for "Silk Stalkings."
- [Crow] Hi, Larry, I love your show.
- Cummings, get me to Mistretta.
(Tom grunting)
Mistretta, what's this
about a load of merchandise
I'm supposed to be shipping in?
- [Tom] What about all the merchandise?
- I got cops sitting on me,
they told me this and I don't know it.
(Tom mimicking phone call)
- You what?
- [Crow] You're wearing what?
Is it sheer?
- Get over here and don't argue with me.
- [Joel] Not that quickly.
Oh, nose candy.
- [Cummings] Let's drive around the block.
- [Tom] Hi Dad.
- [Crow] Loved you in "The
Taking of Pelham One Two Three."
- [Joel] Hey, you want the radio?
"King Biscuit Flour Hour" is on.
- What's bugging you?
- Listen you punk, for the future,
next time you start something,
you tell me before you
start it, not afterwards.
Now ship the dope someplace else,
I've got this cop on my tail.
- [Tom] It's just that Mitchell guy.
- What's on the water, Cummings?
- What's on the water?
- [Crow] Smoke.
- Merchandise.
- It's not coming through my facilities.
- It can't go nowhere else.
- Why not?
Because that's the way
Mr. Gallano wants it.
♫ Uh-huh, uh-huh ♫
- Because maybe it's in
San Pedro now or tomorrow.
It's too late, Cummings.
- [Tom] Hey look, an Applebee's.
- If it comes through San
Pedro, I'm not gonna touch it.
As of now I will not touch it.
- [Tom] (laughing) Oh.
- Cummings, you are not in a
position to say such things.
- [Tom] You can't handle the truth!
- Before you open your big mouth again,
you better think of Mr. Gallano.
- [Crow] Oh, this may be the wrong route.
Are you Steve?
- I say it boy, because I mean it.
- [Tom] Let's go do that little expedition
we were thinking about.
- [Joel] Okay.
Okay now you guys, we've
got about three minutes
before we're due back in the theater,
so we gotta do this outward bound
experience toot sweet, okay?
Servo, you know the drill.
- Roger.
Joel lowers us into the refuse trench
and we have but 90 seconds
to field strip ourselves
and reassemble ourselves while
dangling by our po' poles
in the stinky darkness.
Ready?
- Uh huh, Commander Crow, you ready?
(growls)
(Tom talking)
- You kids be careful.
- Don't worry ma'am, we'll
bring them back alive.
Let's go!
♫ Action Jackson is the name ♫
- Bye!
Bye, see you later!
Oh!
Oh, uh the light, uh guys?
Guys?
And the evil underpants, hey guys?
Oh.
Uh, hello, sirs?
- Don't worry doctor, I
knew when we brought him on
we'd have to eliminate
him, that's half the fun.
- Yes, Frank, but how?
These things must be done delicately.
(evil laughing)
- After all, he knew going in that this
was only a temporary situation.
- Yes, and now I want
this temporary situation
taken care of, permanently.
(evil laughing)
- Are we talking about the same thing?
- He's been a canker sore
on my gum line for too long.
- The way he struts around
like he owns the place, pah!
- Let's use method number 53, hmm?
- Yes.
Elegant, painful.
- And leaves nothing behind
but the great smell of brute.
(evil laughing)
- Let's do it now.
- No no, patience, my little henchman.
Let's wait until after the experiment.
- And spring it, make him
work for it, and then!
- And then, our little
be-jumpsuited fool will be history!
(evil laughing)
Get back to work!
- Jumpsuit!
Fool!
They're going to kill Joel,
they're going to kill Joel!
They're going to kill Joel, help!
What do we do, what do we do?
I gotta get him out of here,
they're gonna kill him.
Help!
Easy girl, take it easy.
Calm down, breathe through your nose.
(sighing)
Here we go, that does
it, easy does it, okay,
okay, okay,
okay.
Okay, okay.
They're going to kill Joel!
(screaming)
("Love Theme from MST3K")
- [Tom] That was fun.
(voices on police radio)
- [Joel] Good job.
- Log this report, timed
- [Tom] Uh Mitchell, hello?
- 24:17 hours.
I'm at the Deaney residence.
I'm putting my gun in the glove
compartment and locking it.
- [Joel] Just had a french dip.
- [Voiceover] 55, what's
that supposed to mean?
55, repeat?
- If I'm shot in the next couple of hours,
I was unarmed when it happened.
Log it, 55 out.
- [Crow] Man, speaking of logging it,
I better find a bush around here.
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] Mitchell!
Mitchell, Mitchell, Mitchell.
Mitchell.
- [Joel] Hey, hi Mitchell!
- [Tom] Go about your business.
Hey Mitchell!
- [Joel] Shh.
(mimicking dogs howling)
- [Joel] Uh honey, Mitchell's here.
- [Crow] Whoa, is that a beer?
- [Tom] Weight on my
chest, my hand's tingling.
- [Joel] Oh shoot, a door,
I didn't plan on this.
- [Tom] Man I love this, I
got soap, I got dog poopy.
- [Crow] This week's practical joke.
The victim, John Saxon.
(mimicking heavy breathing)
- [Joel] Man, if I could
just sit in a lawn chair
for five minutes, that's all I need.
- [Crow] What a clean garage,
no bikes, sleds, or oil spots.
- [Tom] Do you know who did it?
Have you figured it out yet?
(eerie music)
(whistling)
- [Joel] Uh Mitchell,
do you want to come in?
(mimicking dog whimpering)
(mimicking dog panting)
- [Tom] Liquid metal.
- [Joel] Reynolds Wrap.
Keeps freshness in,
can't keep Mitchell out.
(dramatic music)
♫ Oh, you're a holiday ♫
- [Crow] Well, that's my plan.
- [Joel] I smell crab dip.
- [Crow] Melmac?
Why would he be collecting Melmac?
- [Tom] An empty plate brakes my heart.
- [Crow] Keith Haring was here.
- [Joel] Oh, yeah.
Try for a quick 40 winks here.
- [Tom] It means the
victim was Jack Valenti!
- [Joel] What are you doing Mitchell?
(dramatic music)
- [Crow] Why are they
playing "Nadia's Theme?"
- [Tom] Or "The Young and the Restless."
That's a reach, huh.
- [Crow] Just browsing.
(Tom yelling)
♫ Mitchell, Mitchell
♫ Keep your eye on the sammich
♫ Mitchell, heart's pounding
♫ Mitchell, veins clogging, Mitchell ♫
(mimicking funk music)
- [Joel] Oh man, this is hard to do
after six sour cream burritos!
- [Crow] The cloistered
life is not for me.
- Huh?
- What?
- [Joel] Would you give me that?
- [Crow] It's Fish!
- Tyzack?
- [Tom] We can't name a
series after you, sorry.
- See him off.
- [Joel] Hey, he looks like a
guy from a Dave Berg cartoon.
- What in the hell are you up to?
- Deaney.
- What'd I tell you, I
told you to forget Deaney.
Do you know who he is?
- Yeah, he's a trade union lawyer.
- And I gave you a direct
order to forget him.
Now why did I give you that order?
- [Crow] And none of that "I dunno."
- I'm gonna tell you why.
Every federal law violation--
- [Tom] Every federal law violation!
- Against Deaney and his trade union.
I've been working on this
thing for over two years.
In the meantime, you get
back out there on Cummings,
and you stay with him.
Deaney is FBI property.
- Right boss.
- [Joel] And find my upper
lip while you're out there!
- [Crow] (laughing) A little
peek into Mitchell's life.
- [Tom] Damn, it's almost time for Bozo.
- [Joel] Yeah, go for the gusto, Mitchell.
- [Tom] Is that you, Ma?
- [Crow] Bo Derek!
- [Greta] Hello.
- Hi.
- I'm your friend.
- [Joel] Well, Linda Evans, actually.
- Friend?
- [Tom] I'm selling Yanni tapes.
- [Joel] Uh, just gotta
adjust my Roscoe here.
- [Mitchell] Come on in, friend.
- [Crow] Where's John Derek?
Should we set another place for him?
- [Tom] So do you work at
a petting zoo? (sniffing)
- [Joel] Uncle Fester?
- [Tom] Oh.
- So you want a drink?
- What do you have?
- Beer and vodka.
- Beer.
- [Crow] You like 'em half empty?
Some of them got cigarettes in them.
(romantic music)
- [Tom] Oh, this is so embarrassing,
he’s playing a Kitaro album.
- [Joel] Uh, sorry about the porn.
There’s a Kilgore Trout piece in there.
- [Tom] I wouldn't sit
there, other side please.
- [Crow] There's some
chips under the cushion,
help yourself.
- Don't you think I'm as
good as anything here?
- [Tom] Well, uh, you
got an airbrush on ya?
- You got me wrong, I'd like a glass.
- [Joel] Okay your majesty.
- [Crow] I got these at Conoco.
They got Dick Butkus on them.
- [Tom] Ooh, ooh.
- You want a towel?
- [Crow] No, I'll use the curtains.
- Wanna lick it off?
- [Joel] Absolutely not!
- [Tom] Well she was gonna
smell like beer sooner or later.
- Sorry, the beer got a little excited.
- [Crow] That's okay, we can just cuddle.
- [Joel] What?
- [Joel And Robots] Oh.
- [Tom] Jeez.
Sorry, I'm a really unappealing man.
- [Crow] So, more beer?
(Joel sighing)
("Love Theme from MST3K")
♫ It's Bugsy Malone ♫
(laughing)
- [Crow] It's Fred.
(door closing)
What was that?
Oh.
- [Tom] Oh, we're taking
the boys to play group.
- [Crow] Nice cap.
♫ Mobsters laughing, really smiling
♫ A man selling heroin ♫
- [Joel] Ah, the spotted cuckoo
bird is flying backwards.
- [Crow] It's a cold day for pontooning.
- Hello, Mr. Gallano.
- [Tom] I'm not Rappaport.
- Last night I had to come to my home.
Salvatore Mistretta, my cousin.
- [Crow] 'Cause I'm-a Italian you know?
(man talking)
- He's a punk.
- [Crow] Did I tell you I'm Italian?
Let me restate that.
- Who convinced you to
finance that hijack?
If you want drugs you can
draw 'em, you can buy 'em.
- [Joel] Hey, where's Ruth Buzzi?
- Stealing is greedy.
- May I remind you of something?
- [Crow] I'm-a from Italy.
- Sure.
- In August of 1963,
you, me and some others,
we had a very fine meeting.
- [Crow] He was hastily
put together, wasn't he?
- In which we allowed you
influence in this area
in exchange for certain
assignments to be handled by you.
- So?
- That was very generous, yes?
- [Tom] Oui?
- Fair enough.
- Now it's your turn.
♫ To be what-a you can be ♫
- It would take delivery
of Salvatore's shipments
through your contacts at the port, okay?
- I'm not bringing that
shipment in, and that is final.
- [Tom] The shipment's in!
- [Joel] Well, time for
my step aerobics class.
- [Crow] Hey boss, you really did great.
Your personal skills are something.
- [Tom] Hold it in, hold it in.
- [Joel] I'm almost Anthony Quinn.
- [Crow] Was Merlin ever
in the Dave Clark Five?
- [Tom] It was a big
time, when big men drove
nothing but huge foreign cars.
- [Crow] See, huh.
(car honking)
- [Joel] Honey, I'm home.
Had that meeting with the gangster.
- [Crow] Mitchell is one
of the great followers.
- Mitchell, I made a decision about you.
I got a lot of things on
my mind at the moment.
And you're getting too heavy to carry.
- I'm sorry you feel
that way, Mr. Cummings.
- I do.
Now you gonna get lost or not?
- Well I'd like to, but
there are some questions--
- You're saying no?
- I'm saying no.
- Thought I'd give you the chance.
- [Tom] That was sweet,
he didn't have to do that.
Thanks.
- [Joel] Uh, say boss, you
think Mitchell likes me?
- [Crow] Shut up and drive.
- Is your friend ready?
- Yes sir, he's ready.
- [Joel] Who, Rosey Grier?
- [Tom] This is what I'll remember
when I think of the movie "Mitchell."
And I will think of it.
- [Crow] Oh wait, I lost him.
Oh nope, there he is.
- [Joel] Mitchell, even his
name says, "Is that a beer?"
(laughing)
- [Crow] You know they're easy to follow
when they use their turn signal.
- [Joel] Man, why don't they just
tie their bumpers together?
(laughing)
- [Tom] It's not an official chase scene
without the waka-jo-waka.
- [Crow] Yeah.
Hot merging action!
(suspenseful music)
- [Joel] Oh goodness,
they merged successfully,
my heart was in my throat.
Mitchell.
- [Tom] Jeez, these guys
couldn't shake a trolley.
- [Crow] This makes "Driving Miss Daisy"
look like "Bullitt."
(dramatic music)
- [Tom] Next week on
Mitchell, the clover leaf.
And today, 3M is a vibrant
company, combining innovation,
effective risk management,
and marketing, 3M.
- [Joel] Oh boy they're traveling
at speeds of up to 25 miles per hour.
- [Crow] I've seen faster
funeral processions.
- [Tom] The only really exciting thing
is that "Vanishing Point" is being filmed
on the other side of the canyon.
- [Joel] Oh, this is nice,
they're using the light rock
for the chase scene rather
than the grunge sound.
- [Tom] I like the light rock.
- [Crow] Finally, the
chase scene's pace car.
- [Tom] Yes, the Lincoln Continental,
perfect for off-road excitement.
(exciting music)
- [Crow] I can't shake 'em, boss.
Here, I'll lightly touch
the brake and accelerate.
(laughing)
- [Joel] Hey, get out of our chase scene!
- [Tom] The vicious Mustang culls
the weak ones from the herd.
(car accelerating)
- [Crow] Hey are you Mitchell?
Can I have your autograph?
- [Joel] Well so pass if
you're gonna, come on!
- [Tom] Excuse me, may I cut in?
May I have this chase?
(laughing)
- [Joel] Uh, do you have
any facial expressions?
- [Crow] Haha, this is fun, ha.
- [Joel] Larry Miller.
- [Tom] So why does he keep
downshifting from automatic?
Kind of a hot rod "Ben-Hur."
- [Joel] Yeah, as a matter
of fact I do own the road.
- [Crow] Hey, the headlight fixed itself.
- [Tom] Hey, it's Mitchell!
- [Crow] Your thing is dragging!
- [Joel] Mitchell Miller.
- [Tom] I know a little
shortcut down here, oh.
- [Joel] Mitchell.
- [Crow] Uh, shouldn't
we exchange information?
- [Tom] Ah, that shook
up the beers pretty bad.
(slow guitar music)
- [Crow] Hey, cut out that
"Rockford" music, I'm Mitchell!
- [Tom] Mitchell.
- [Joel] Hey, it's a booze pool.
- [Tom] I'll have a
vodka chlorine, please.
- [Rudy] Yeah?
- Rudy,
- [Crow] Tooty.
- I got pressure.
- Who's pushing?
- Mistretta.
- Mistretta?
You can handle him.
- Well there are problems.
- Unless of course he's backed by Gallano.
- You got it.
- What the hell are you calling me for?
- [Joel] I'm getting dizzy.
- [Tom] Yeah.
- Well I'll tell ya, it's
about a little discussion
between me and Mistretta.
- [Crow] Or Gallano.
- [Rudy] Give me the
short answer, Cummings.
- [Tom] Mistretta.
- You wanna get the same
answer off any of the boys.
If Gallano's involved
- [Crow] Or Mistretta.
- I don't want any part of it.
- [Tom] Or Gallano.
That was Mistretta.
- This is all gonna blow up pretty soon,
and when it does, who've
we got on our side?
- [Joel And Robots] Ghostbusters!
- [Cummings] If he's still around.
- He's not on our side, sir.
- Yes he is.
I'm no good to him dead.
("Love Theme from MST3K")
- O-E-P-E-O-P
E-O-E, oh, working like a dog.
Got to think how to
get Joel off this ship.
How to get Joel off?
Charter flight?
No.
How, how, how to get Joel off this ship,
but how?
Boy I'm frustrated.
Well, back at it.
Throw him?
No.
- Hey Gypsy.
Working on a project, huh?
Have you seen my "Inside the
PGA" around here anywhere?
- No Joel, I haven't seen
your magazine anywhere.
- Oh, it's got this great
article on Fuzzy Zoeller.
- Joel, if you were faced
with your imminent death
and had to get back to Earth like, pronto,
how would you do it?
- Oh come on, I'd never leave you.
- But Joel, your imminent death!
- Gypsy honey, I could never leave you.
It's all for one and one for all,
that's the Robinson way.
- Oh no.
- Huh, Fuzzy Zoeller, what a great guy.
- Oh, oh I can't tell Joel.
He would never leave.
I'm alone with my heavy burden.
(crying)
Wait, I've got Tom and Crow to help me.
I'm sure in a pinch I can depend on them
to be serious and calm
and intelligent and--
(Crow talking)
- Okay, what's next, what's next?
- Okay, "Hardcastle and McCormick."
- Okay.
♫ Ride, ridin' like the demon
that drives your dreams ♫
- Yeah, that's it.
(laughing)
Hey, what you doing, Gyps?
- This is very, very, very important.
- There's the guitar lick,
(Tom mimicking guitar riff).
- Wait, can you two keep a secret?
- No.
- Never could, never will, Gypsy!
(laughing)
Okay, Crow, how about "Bonanza?"
Including the words!
- Oh, okay!
♫ It's alright if I pick
a little fight, bonanza ♫
- Oh goodness.
Oh, I'm being tested.
Oh,
who, who is testing Gypsy?
Hello?
Well, I will prevail because I am good
and the mans are evil.
But, (screaming).
(beeping)
Oh, you guys got movie light.
(screaming)
(sighing)
- [Tom] What's eating juicy?
- [Joel] Hey, want to do
something later maybe?
- [Mitchell] Got the correct time?
- [Tom] Yeah, 10 two.
Tend to your damn business.
- 10 to 12.
- [Crow] Noon or midnight?
- That guy Cummings sure gets around.
Sure is some schedule he's got.
- Don't talk to me mister.
- The antisocial type, huh?
Private type?
Then you should let other
people have their privacy.
- [Crow] My face hurts.
- [Joel] What was that all about?
(gunfire)
- [Crow] Ah, Daryl Gates on his day off.
- [Tom] Hey, I'm putting here.
- [Crow] He's landed
just short of the green.
- [Joel] Oh no, Mr.
Trevino's been hit again!
(man groaning)
- [Crow] (laughing) Isn't that cute,
he's trying to tell us something!
- [Tom] Can we play through?
We got a hot one back here.
- You wanna hold this?
I gotta go call headquarters.
- [Joel] That Merlin
is lost without a map.
- [Crow] Don't laugh,
you're only encouraging him.
- [Joel] (laughing) Mitchell, oh.
(ominous music)
- [Tom] The new Chrysler Fury,
the car that thinks it's a house.
- [Joel] I can't believe it,
I'm in trouble for killing us a civilian.
- Mitchell, I thought
your job was Cummings.
- I've been busy.
- Oh really?
- Yeah, you think I would
have (Mitchell mumbling)
- Nope, you may be facing
a disciplinary charge
for shooting him.
- What the hell, you wanted
him for two weeks, no bail,
that's how you got him.
- I didn't expect you to shoot him.
- Oh you were asking that, Aldridge.
- [Crow] I thought I
had authority over him!
- [Cummings] You shouldn't have
blown your cover like that.
I'll go phone headquarters.
- [Tom] Pass the potatoes,
the peas, the butter,
the peas, the pie, the butter.
(man talking)
Oh trouble, oh pass the
gravy, the stuffing.
- Don't forget Mr. Mitchell.
- [Joel] (spitting)
Oh, that's one of mine.
- [Crow] This is the part
of being a henchman I hate.
- [Tom] Can I tempt you with some dessert?
- I don't think Benton likes you.
- [Joel] Uh, can we get more
volume on that jacket please?
- That's the trouble, not
too many people like you.
You ought to cultivate
people, go out to them.
With your confidence, you never know
when they're gonna come in useful.
You've gotta be nice to them.
- [Tom] Oh, nice, more butter please.
- Well what about the
heroin, Mr. Cummings?
- Forget the heroin.
- [Joel] That's for dessert!
- Don't talk about the
heroin over the soup.
That's your trouble, you're impatient.
Now you're aware that guy
Zippy's gonna do some harm.
- I wanted to find out who he was.
- Well ask him, don't shoot him.
Who was he?
- [Tom] Well I didn't ask him, I shot him.
- Uh, Booker, got Booker.
- [Crow] Booker's a good cop!
- Booker, Booker, Booker?
- [Tom] Who's got the Booker?
- No, Bocca, with a double C.
Edmundo Bocca.
- Like the soup?
- [Crow] Goes with my pie.
- [Mitchell] Yes.
You got this place laid out
like a real banquet, Mr. Cummings.
- For a business dinner.
We might talk business later.
Can I have some more soup, Benton?
- There is no more soup, sir.
- [Joel] I sense he's lying,
but why would he lie about the soup?
- How do you like that, in
my own house, no more soup.
- [Tom] My dinner with Mitchell.
- Bocca works for Mistretta.
- That's the first piece of information
you've come up with, Mr. Cummings.
- [Crow] How 'bout letting us in on some?
- Benton, what are you
doing with those steaks,
are you growing them?
- [Tom] (laughing sarcastically)
You can't grow steaks.
- [Crow] Oh wait, I want the bone marrow.
- [Joel] Oh, boom mike, big time, whoo.
- You gonna take all
night peeling that orange?
- I thought maybe we might
talk about the shipment.
- [Tom] Would you just
give me that orange?
- [Crow] I have a new friend.
- [Joel] Uh hey, I put a
couple rolls in my pocket,
is that okay?
- What I want to know is--
- The coffee's cold, Benton,
you're a lousy butler.
- [Benton] I am not a lousy butler!
- You're a lousy butler.
- I am not.
- I say you're a lousy
butler, the coffee is cold.
- [Mitchell] Well I think I gotta go.
- [Tom] It’s "The
Servant" by Harold Pinter.
- [Joel] Oh look, you made Mitchell leave.
- [Tom] Oh man, I'm so hungry.
Only two steaks for dinner,
didn't get to finish my orange.
All the frozen yogurt
places were closed, ugh.
Big buttery moon up there,
sidewalk kind of looks like
ice cream if you squint hard.
Stairs look like cake.
- [Joel] Mitchell's legions of fans
show up at any time of the day or night.
- [Crow] Well, this'll be
okay, I don't see, oof!
- [Joel] Jeez, those Jehovah’s
Witnesses are getting tough!
- [Tom] Whoa.
Now they're gonna end up with
Mitchell's dinner all over them.
(men struggling)
Oh wait, hold it, a little piece of bacon.
- [Joel] You know is it wrong
for me to want to see this?
- [Crow] Uh, nope.
- [Tom] Ooh, right in the
tenderloin steak region.
- [Crow] Oh, sorry bud, we
thought you were Rockford.
- [Tom] Oh, I think this
is rice, oh, no it's not.
(laughing)
- [Joel] Well, ol’
Mitchell sure got his self
hogtied and railroaded there.
♫ My my my my Mitchell
♫ What would your mama say ♫
(man talking under sheets)
- [Crow] Oh, he's alone reading
a comic book under there.
(upbeat music)
- [Tom] Mitchell honey, do you have any
new age or something?
- [Joel] Oh, he's sleeping
with Helen Keller.
- [Crow] Oh, how I long for
"The Burning Bed" right now.
- [Tom] You got a lot of junk around here.
♫ Well oh my my my Mitchell ♫
- [Crow] Why would anyone want
to do this with Mitchell, Joel?
- [Joel] Shh.
A vase or two faces?
- [Tom] Oh Yanni, I mean
John, I mean Mitchell!
♫ Oh my my my Mitchell
♫ You shoot 'em just to get 'em in jail ♫
- [Joel] Hey watch this,
I learned this in college,
check this out, beer cans.
- [Tom] That's class.
(mimicking can opening and chugging)
- [Joel] Baby oil!
(all screaming)
(Tom throwing up)
♫ My my my God, no ♫
- [Joel] Could you maybe
get aroused, Mitchell?
(Joel trails off)
(robots crying)
Um, how about some BTO?
- You went through that Tuesday.
- [Tom] And I still
don't have any Tic Tacs.
- But this is Thursday.
- [Crow] He makes a good point.
(sighing)
- You're gonna get busted for this.
- Guy that busted me would
have to be very straight.
- You implying that I'm not straight?
(Joel laughing)
- [Joel] You're boozy, but lovable.
(woman mumbling)
- The only trouble is you don't know it.
- You really think I'd take
some sort of a payoff, huh?
- You already have, haven't you?
- Oh wait a minute.
So you're a Christmas gift.
- [Crow] And I wanted a Super Soaker.
- That's what you said.
- Did I?
- [Mitchell] Didn't you?
Damn right.
That doesn't make me the cooperative type.
You just watch your pretty mouth.
- So bust me.
You're a policeman and that's grass.
- [Crow] Merlin Olsen
sent him that painting.
(laughing)
- [Joel] My Mitchell,
I think I'll keep him.
- [Greta] Oh, come on.
Come on.
- [Crow] Ew.
Are they done, can I look?
- You sure know how to bring a girl down.
- [Tom] Double room please, one night.
- He sleeps with me then busts me.
- [Crow] First things first!
- Well she asked me to.
- What, sleep with her or bust her?
- Both.
(Joel mimicking a sad trombone)
(officer talking)
- When your case is heard,
are there any other offenses you'd like
for us to take into consideration
while you're in this kind of a mood?
- Yeah, being hung up on this guy.
- That's a mistake, lady.
- [Tom] Didn't do me any good.
- Not an offense.
- When can I see my lawyer?
- We'll take care of it for you.
- [Joel] You're sleeping
with him at three.
(police officer talking)
- Hey, that's only a $500 fine.
For $1,000 a night, you're still a hit.
- [Crow] Not after taxes.
- Oh, you're a terrific human being.
I had a clean record in this town.
- [Tom] Sirens!
- Hey.
- Make sure she signs
the property receipt.
- [Crow] Nobody asked for a prostitute,
we can take her right away!
- [Joel] Are we still on for Tuesday?
- Hey.
You really sleep with her?
- Yep.
- [Crow] And then I kissed her.
- [Tom] Hey Wally.
- [Crow] Mitch.
(car honking)
- [Joel] At Beneficial
you're good for more.
(car honking)
- [Tom] The declining years of Lee Majors.
- Ask him to come in.
Say that it's important,
say that I have to see him.
- Yes sir.
- [Crow] Tell him we have sour cream.
- [Joel] Oh man, this
stakeout's getting crowded.
- [Tom] Hi folks.
- [Crow] Duh, the steaks are ready.
- [Tom] Can Linda come too?
- [Joel] So tell me Merlin,
do you know Roman Gabriel?
- [Crow] I think you're a good butler.
♫ Movin' on up ♫
- [Tom] Weezy!
- This way.
- [Joel] To Wall Drug.
- You want a drink?
- [Joel] Is the Pope Catholic?
- [Cummings] Sit down.
- [Crow] Wanna shoot a beer bong?
- Alright, Mitchell.
Why don't we stop messing around.
- What's that gonna mean?
- I wanna put you on the payroll.
- [Tom] We have an opening in retail.
- I'm in trouble.
You sensed it, you know it, and I know it.
- Specifically what trouble?
- Well, the idea of the payroll,
now I get to ask the questions.
- [Tom] Noted.
- I need help.
- [Joel] I've got a
purple mole on my back.
- I need help from any
source that I can get it.
- [Crow] So I'm down to you.
- Well put it on the line.
- I wanna buy your services.
Your voice on the phone in case I need
the help of your police department.
- Let me just uh, write the details
of your bribe down, Mr. Cummings.
- [Joel] It's a Shriner car!
- [Crow] Oh, a place in the shade!
(cars bumping)
Ooh!
He pulled out right in front of me!
- [Joel] She's got a
David Cassidy haircut.
- [Crow] She's gonna write
"REDRUM" on his windshield.
Heh, red, oh.
- [Joel] He'll think of me the whole time
he's cleaning that off.
Uh, were you expecting a prostitute?
- [Crow] Word on the
street is you're a jerk!
- Could be open.
Cash?
Or subtle, just the way you
take it from other people.
- Uh, I don't take bribes.
(Tom talking over Cummings)
- City Hall they saw you this morning
with a hooker that you sleep
with and occasionally arrest.
- What else they tell you?
- She's too expensive,
you can't afford her
on a policeman's salary.
Now somebody's picking up the check.
Who could that be?
- You?
- Me what?
- You're picking up the check.
- No I don't, I don't pay
for your hookers Mitchell.
- [Tom] Well, could you?
- Then who is?
- You mean you don't know?
You're a cop (laughing)
and you don't know?
- [Tom] (laughing) No, I don't.
- [Crow] I specifically
came here for dinner.
(snapping)
- [Joel] Get me some
flowers pronto, Merlin.
- [Tom] I'm not leaving
without some tuna wiggle.
- [Crow] He's gotta light
him in his bald spot.
- [Tom] Someone to see you, sir.
- I knew you'd call sooner or later.
- [Joel] So, are you ready
to join Hair Club yet?
- Come on in.
- [Tom] Joe Don Baker, face number four.
- [Joel] Hey, Joe Don.
- [Crow] Hey, hey, no.
- Sit down.
- [Joel] Prostitute?
- How do you like your scotch?
- [Crow] Uh, by the quart.
- [Joel] Come on more,
come on, keep it coming,
I'm a big boy, that's right.
- [Tom] I usually take it
with a Ding Dong in it,
but I guess I’ll take
it neat, that’s okay.
- You know--
- [Joel] Booze is good food.
- [Deaney] I admire a man like you.
- [Crow] Not you, specifically.
- You take your time,
you're cool.
Yes sir.
- [Joel] You know he may be a bad guy,
but he's got a ton of gifts up there.
- How's the broad?
- That's what I came to talk about.
- You know what it
costs to keep you sweet?
A hundred bucks an hour.
Tells me it happens all night.
But you figured out,
that's like a thousand
bucks before breakfast.
- As far as I'm concerned,
she's just some broad
looking for a little action.
(laughing)
- You wanna see the receipts?
- You're wasting your money, Deaney.
- Let me be the judge of that.
- She'll lie on my bed for nothing.
- [Tom] Well, I guess I'll
have to talk to my accountant.
- You really think so?
- [Joel] I'm turning Japanese.
- [Crow] Let me show you
what I got for Christmas.
- I arranged a hundred
dollar company in your name.
- [Joel] You mean Orion?
- I negotiate the transfer
of a piece of real estate.
- [Crow] Cross to fireplace.
- Well let's say,
- [Tom] I'm Rosalind Russell.
- $25,000.
You haven't got $25,000 but
I'll get you a bank loan.
All legitimate.
The real estate you buy
will be a piece I designate
and you'll buy it from one
of my subsidiary companies.
- [Joel] Oh man, I'm so lost.
- [Deaney] Then,
I'll buy it off you, for
let's say, a hundred Gs.
That'll give you a
clear profit of $75,000.
And who's to say it isn't
a genuine investment?
- [Tom] Is that a Slim Jim?
Can I have that?
Are you done with that?
- [Crow] Do you open
your Christmas presents
on Christmas Eve or Christmas morning?
- Well?
What do you think?
- I'm gonna get you for that murder.
- [Joel] But first, merry Christmas.
- Or I'll die trying.
- You're making the biggest
mistake of your life.
("Love Theme from MST3K")
- [Joel] Yep, another
Wednesday night at Mitchell's.
- [Crow] Our hero, ladies and gentlemen.
- [Tom] And I'm still not drunk.
♫ Life should be ♫
- [Joel] Oh my goodness, I
think BJ Thomas is in his room!
(smarmy music)
(Crow slurping)
- [Crow] Oh yuck, I got
a cigarette in that one.
- [Tom] I like to top off my beer drinking
with another beer, it's like dessert.
- [Joel] It's a very special
Joe Don Baker Christmas.
(Crow grunting and farting)
- [Joel] Hey, oh hey!
Booze and I are buying a house together,
we're gonna move in.
- [Crow] He’s gonna strip down
to his underwear and watch "McQ."
- [Tom] Huh, wonder what
this thing does here.
Water, I never knew that, wow!
(Crow laughing)
- [Crow] Oh thank God for the jump cut.
(voices on radio)
(honking)
- [Joel] Honey, church!
- [Crow] Mitchell, I'm not going
to your folks' for Christmas!
- [Tom] Man, I'm still
in this Mitchell movie.
- [Joel] Adam Rich!
(Crow groaning)
- Hi.
Are you the man from the insurance?
- No.
- He came last night.
- Oh?
- My mother doesn't like you.
- Well I don't like your mother.
- Why not?
- [Mitchell] Why not?
- Yeah, why not?
- No, why not?
- Why are you repeating what I say?
- [Tom] Tonight on "Crossfire."
- [Mitchell] Why are you
repeating what I say?
- I'm not!
- Well I'm not.
- [Boy] You are.
- Buzz off.
- What?
- [Mitchell] What?
- What'd you say?
- [Boy] Did you say something?
- Did you say something?
(Tom screaming)
- You're lying through your teeth.
- You're your lying through your teeth.
- [Mitchell] Buzz off, huh?
- Buzz off!
- Buzz off, kid!
- [Crow] The inspiration
for "Cop and a Half."
(Mitchell yelling)
- [Tom] Give him a half block head start,
then I'm gonna mow him over.
- [Joel] Oh, Schlitz would
listen to me right now,
that’s for sure.
(upbeat music)
♫ Did you ever have to make up your mind ♫
- [Joel] The Loving Handful.
- Why don't you have me arrested?
- Because you want me to.
Nah, I don't want you
on an assault charge,
I want everything, I
want you and Mistretta
and a lead to Gallano
and the lousy heroin.
- [Crow] A family, a career.
- Maybe you'll get them.
I wonder if I should have
a talk with you Mitchell.
- I wonder if you should too, Cummings.
- You just gotta come in the house.
- No.
- I give you my word nothing
will happen to you in there.
- I'm not scared of you, open up.
- [Joel] But I do have to use your washer,
if that's alright.
- [Tom] Let's get back inside
before that kid comes back again.
- [Crow] No Claude Akins, but what a butt!
- [Joel] Mitchell.
- Sit down.
- Well--
- Shut up son, you don't drink do you?
- [Joel] Just pour, Dad.
- Well, this is the way it went.
Mistretta made this set up.
- [Joel] With Gallano.
- Gonna be too late to
tell me that the heroin
was on the water coming to
my operation in San Pedro.
Now, he tells me the stuff
is already on its way.
- [Joel] From Mistretta.
(Mitchell talking)
- Well,
- [Tom] Don't close it,
don't close it!
- Mistretta phoned a little while back.
- [Joel] Oh, you mean Gallano.
- With an ultimatum, I
have an hour to reply.
- What are you going to do?
- I'm gonna think, Mitchell.
Then I'm gonna call Mistretta back
and tell him it was okay
to use my port facilities.
- [Crow] Port, you've got port here?
- I'm gonna set it up,
hand it over to you.
- [Crow] Ta-da!
- That sounds just a
little too good to be true.
- It might.
- How's their stuff gonna come in?
- Well a rich woman in a big car
is gonna pick up the
luggage that she sent ahead
after her vacation in Acapulco,
you're gonna be the chauffeur.
- [Joel] Well, it's
gonna be $3.50 an hour.
- Your rendezvous with Mistretta.
- [Crow] Gallano.
- [Mitchell] Where is it?
- He has a house in Calabasas.
Now you get the heroin, you get Mistretta.
You don't get me, understood?
You don't get me.
- Alright, what time does
this start happening?
- [Crow] No time like the present.
- [Tom] Oh, it's too bad
that scene had to end, eh?
- [Crow] Rich woman, big car, see, see?
♫ Sweet Adeline ♫
- [Crow] Oh Mitchell, no!
- [Joel] Oh, be careful
with that horse, young man.
- We'll need your
signature, here, here, here,
initials here,
and if you'll fill out
this customs declaration.
- [Woman] And what do
I write under contents?
- Personal.
- [Joel] Oh, what time
does your shift end?
- And value?
- $100.
- [Crow] No, I mean street value, punk.
- [Joel] Wow, that Mitchell is
really a master of disguise.
- [Crow] Just had a
nice chat with your mom.
- [Tom] Take me to Wendy's,
I’m meeting Clara Peller.
- [Joel] We're going
to control the ghetto,
you and I, young man.
- [Tom] Just keep driving, Hoke.
- [Crow] I can't wear yellow.
- [Joel] Yes you can.
Guys, he's got a terracotta
bowling pin lamp.
- [Crow] Certainly does.
(phone ringing)
- [Man] Yeah.
- Let me talk to Mistretta.
- [Man] For you.
- [Tom] Of course it is, it's my phone.
Give me that.
Gallano here.
- Okay Mistretta, the
consignment's on its way.
- I hope everything goes smooth.
- There's one slight
alteration in the arrangement.
Do you know that cop that's
been bugging me, Mitchell?
He's bringing you the stuff.
- I don't believe you.
- Do.
- [Mistretta] Are you out of your mind?
- I'm gonna be out on my boat.
- [Crow] Ha!
- You just tie up all the loose ends.
Mitchell knows about it.
Get the stuff, and deal
with him in your own way.
- [Joel] Boss is such a dick.
- [Crow] I'd better call Mom.
- Oh uh Sergeant, you might
want to tell Chief Pallin
that one of his boys,
that Mitchell character,
- [Tom] Oh, the drunk one.
- Well he's heading for
trouble in Calabasas.
- [Tom] That's the cop that
sleeps with hookers, right?
- [Crow] Oh, I just felt
the balloon break, oh!
- [Joel] I thought maybe
we could just stop here
and just talk.
- [Mitchell] Step out?
- [Tom] You know how
fast you were driving?
- [Joel] Look, I was.
- [Crow] Okay, get in.
- [Tom] Alright, let's see the skag.
Here, let me explain
what you're gonna see.
Now I only wear that on special occasions.
(awkward laughing)
- [Crow] Those are my fine washables.
- [Joel] Jeez, Scarface
didn’t do that much at once.
(laughing)
- I didn't have anything
to do with all this.
- You mean this heroin?
- Yes.
- It ain't smack lady, it's chalk.
Cummings is crossing Gallano.
- [Tom] And we're passing
the savings on to you.
- You sure you wanna be
in the middle of this?
- [Joel] I can take the heat.
- Come on, take a walk, huh?
- [Woman] Walk?
- Walk!
- [Tom] But my varicose veins!
- [Mitchell] Come on!
- [Crow] But my hip!
- Watch out for traffic.
- [Tom] What a nice young man.
Bite me, Mitchell.
- [Joel] Quality is job one, yep.
- [Tom] Oh, he's gonna take a little nip
(Tom talking quietly)
- [Joel] Oh, he's doing a
magic trick with the car.
- [Tom] We've never met before, have we?
- [Crow] He's putting a dickey on his car.
- [Tom] Yeah.
Why did I do that?
- [Crow] I think things are
turning around for old Mitchell.
(laughing)
- [Tom] Just keep walking
lady, I can still see you.
Come on!
- [Joel] Mitchell put a handkerchief
on the back of his car, run!
- [Joel And Robots] Oh no, not that.
(all groaning)
- [Crow] Well you can't say
they look suspicious or anything.
- [Tom] Think they
should have brought food
or clothes or something?
- [Joel] Okay, you guys,
I call no singing the
"Gilligan's Island" theme.
- [Crow] Okay, I'll think of it.
(exciting music)
- [Crow] Eischied,
Eischied.
'Cause it's--
- [Tom] The gods must be crazy, look!
(laughing)
- [Joel] It hurts.
- And so you see, Mike,
that's why we need to bring him down!
- That's amazing Gypsy.
Well we've gotta do something.
Here's a manifest for
the Satellite of Love,
maybe there's something
here that can help.
- Yes, yes, oh yes, oh please,
please, please, please.
- Okay, I assume you tried to gain control
of the escape pod in dock 14.
- Yes, I tried to gain control,
there's an escape pod in dock 14?
- According to this
there's a single occupant
escape pod called the "Deus Ex Machina."
- How could I not see it?
D'oh, stupid, oh!
- I wouldn't blame yourself, Gypsy.
Apparently it's in a
box marked "Hamdingers."
- Well no wonder we didn't see
it, nobody likes Hamdingers.
So how do we get him down, huh?
- I don't know, these
clowns must have control.
Let's try this thing.
Here it is.
If, ah, "The pod is controlled remotely
"at the tectronic panel,"
which must be this thing.
"If direct access from
the satellite is desired,
"security key must be
inserted into the panel
"and the sequence C colon backslash CD
"backslash manual period
E-X-E must be entered."
- Frank's got to have
the key, he loves keys!
- Well great, Frank's got the
keys, so how do I get them?
Hey Frank, can I borrow your keys?
- [Frank] Okay.
- Thanks.
Okay, here we go.
Let's see, C colon backslash,
back, manual E-X-E.
I hate these things.
Okay, it says "Direct access initiated,"
you're on your own, Gypsy.
Uh oh.
- Hey, what did you need my keys for?
- Um, your lights were on.
- Oh, okay.
Hey, I don't have a car!
- Well then what'd you
give me your keys for?
- I dunno, I thought I left my lights on.
- Glad I didn't waste time
shutting off your imaginary lights.
- Well, I'm sorry.
- I've got control!
Ooh, I've got to get moving.
("Love Theme from MST3K")
- [Tom] Wait here.
Oh, I'm alone.
- [Crow] We are two wild and crazy guys!
- [Tom] Don't blow it, don't
blow it, don't blow it.
- [Joel] Hey, we're the
sons of the old lady
you made get out of the car and walk!
- Keys.
- [Crow] You're welcome.
(Tom laughing)
- Cummings says you're a cop.
- [Crow] Well that pretty
much blows my cover.
- [Tom] Where's that green pantsuit?
- Says you're the cop
that keeps following him.
He says kill you.
I think he has a point.
He's leaving on a boat
out of Marina del Rey.
I'm gonna put your body on that boat
and then call the coast guard.
- [Joel] Okay, anything I can do?
- [Mistretta] What made
you come here alone?
- Cummings said you were friendly people.
(Crow mimicking dog growling)
- [Tom] Mm, minty.
- Okay boy, where's the stuff?
- I think I hid it.
- [Mistretta] Where?
- In a john at a gas
station outside the docks.
- Well get in.
(man mumbling)
- [Crow] Can you kick my
other knee to balance it out?
(man yelling)
- [Tom] Whoops, ooh.
(explosion)
- [Joel] Oh, this must
be "Dateline NBC."
(laughing)
- [Tom] Is that the signal?
- [Man] The police, the police are coming!
You hear me, the police are coming!
- [Tom] So, are the police coming?
- [Joel] Guys, let's
take the car, oh yeah.
(gunfire)
- [Crow] Andy Kaufman!
You're so stupid.
- [Joel] Mitchell killed the sound.
- [Tom] They're going
faster than that car chase.
- [Crow] Come back, you're so stupid.
(Tom breathing heavily)
(gunfire)
- [Crow] Now isn't it against the rules
to shoot an opponent in a footrace?
(Crow mimicking motorcycle)
- [Joel] Taxi!
- [Tom] Touchdown!
(gunfire)
(Mitchell screaming)
- [Joel] Oh, like a salami's gonna help.
(gunfire)
- [Crow] Thank you very much.
- [Tom] Mitchell.
- [Crow] Oh, let me see this a minute.
(gunfire)
- [Joel] There went Bronson.
- [Tom] I regret nothing! (chokes)
Come here, Mitchell.
- To Marina del Rey.
- [Joel] Well, okay, you
a cop or a, (stuttering)
- [Tom] Huh? What’s that?
What do you mean you don't
have any Schlitz on board?
- [Crow] We've got to close the beaches!
- [Tom] Mitchell, would
you move over please?
The other way!
- [Joel] Uh, can we turn on the radio?
- [Tom] From maritime polymers for boats
to the fuel in this helicopter,
3M, building the future.
- [Joel] Hey, it’s the Starship
Enterprise in dry dock.
(men talking)
- You get a description?
- [Crow] Yeah it's white and it's a boat.
- You're looking for
the proverbial needle.
- Let's try the harbor master.
- We'll take you in.
- [Tom] 3M, innovation, research.
(men talking)
- [Pilot] Coast guard.
- Any private boat can
outrun the coast guard?
- Maybe?
- It's not good enough.
- [Joel] Oh, you fly this thing then.
- [Crow] Oh, there it is,
no, wait that's it, no.
No there, that's the one.
No wait, I think it's, oh.
- [Tom] It's the miracle acrylic bubble
that makes it possible.
- [Crow] Yeah, they call
me ma ma ma ma Mitchell,
I'm always busting heads,
jumping in and out of bed, you?
- [Tom] Mitchell, you should have
thought of that before we left!
Mitchell goes as big as his life.
- [Crow] Now this looks
positively Baywatchian.
- [Tom] PT 90210.
- [Joel] Hold on!
- [Tom] Old flipper.
- On his way to Mexico
in a white 35 footer.
They got a half hour head
start so we gotta hustle.
- [Tom] We're supposed to go to someplace
called the Pacific Ocean.
Said it's big and blue, it's
got a lot of fish in it.
(exciting music)
- [Tom] Yes, the future belongs to 3M.
- [Joel] Hey, is that Paul
Hogan in the middle there?
- [Crow] You guys get
pretty good benefits?
- [Tom] Boatniks 2: The Final Conflict.
- [Joel] Hey check this
out, my foot is huge!
- [Tom] Give me that.
- [Joel] Oh.
- We got a problem man, (man talking)
80 miles, 40 out and 40 back.
20 minutes we'll be in
Mexican territorial waters,
and no power to arrest anyone.
(Mitchell talking)
Right.
(exciting music)
- [Crow] It's turning into
an episode of "Riptide."
- [Joel] Jimmy Osmond, all grown up.
- [Crow] On "The People's Court."
- [Tom] Martin Balsam:
the Dewar’s profile.
(exciting music)
- It's the yellow thing.
- [Crow] It's been following us!
(men talking)
- How long's this rope on its winch?
- 60 feet.
- [Joel] Here, let me show you
around the rest of the cabin.
- Okay.
Hold it steady.
- [Crow] Quick Steve, hard bank turn now!
- Tell me what you want to do, I'll do it.
- [Joel] I want to jump to my death.
- Tie this rope here, on
the front of that bank.
- Hang on to me.
- [Mitchell] Alright.
- [Tom] Mitchell please, not here, honey!
- [Crow] What a great action hero,
he just pawns off his duties on others.
(exciting music)
- What's the idea?
- You'll see.
- Just over the horizon, Mexican border.
- [Tom] And it’s all here, at
3M's new facility in Mexico.
(men talking)
- Keep going.
- You got 10 minutes
to find that boat, Mac.
We're at the halfway point on fuel.
We'll have to turn back.
- [Tom] Harvesting the
ocean's bounty for the future.
- [Joel] Think those are Schlitz cans?
- [Crow] Things will
work out, Mr. Maxwell.
Maxwell?
(men talking)
- [Joel] Oh, so the
helicopter's chasing the boat.
(Joel trails off)
- Okay, lower that thing.
(men talking)
Lower it all the way down.
- [Tom] Andrew's getting a
little thick around the middle.
- [Joel] Just tell me when
this gets uncomfortable.
- Okay.
- [Tom] I'm huge.
Oof.
- [Crow] Alright, now
jig it off the bottom.
- [Joel] Uh, let's just
not talk for awhile.
- [Tom] I still stand by the
idea of the yellow thing.
- [Joel] The hell?
- [Tom] Check out the rotors.
Oh, awkward.
Wait, oh.
- [Joel And Robots] Oh.
(talking to selves)
- [Tom] I don't get it.
Oh.
- [Crow] Huh?
- [Tom] Mitchell!
("Love Theme from MST3K")
- [Joel] You know I think
things were a lot easier
when Mitchell was just
sitting around outside
Martin Balsam's house.
- [Tom] Yeah.
- [Crow] It would.
(gunfire)
(Tom talking)
(mimicking gunfire)
(gunfire)
(men yelling)
- [Crow] Tell my wife
I love her, Mitchell!
- [Tom] Well, you are gonna lose a few.
(Mitchell yelling)
(Tom mocking Mitchell)
- [Joel] Whoa, I didn't
think you'd be that mad.
- [Tom] He was my partner for seven years.
So.
- [Crow] Looks like
excitement by repetition.
- [Tom] It's the maritime
equivalent of rock climbing.
(gunfire)
- [Joel] Oh, that's weird.
- [Crow] Oh, Steve, oh oh.
- [Tom] Oh, what a mess.
- [Joel] Oh, I could never
do that in gym class.
- [Crow] I dreamed I was Father Murphy.
- [Tom] Um, guys, wasn’t
John Saxon in this movie?
- [Crow] Oh yeah.
- [Joel] Mitchell!
- [Tom] Take the rough housing outside.
- [Crow] He's some kind
of hippie somewhere.
- [Joel] Come here, go
away, come here, go away,
that's a pattern with them.
- [Tom] These Circle Line tours
are getting really brutal.
- [Crow] They are.
- [Joel] We're closed!
(men grunting)
- [Crow] Oh, right in the dinghy.
- [Joel] Ouch.
This is for the soup remark!
- [Crow] Mannix, extra large.
- [Joel] Oh, vaudeville.
- [Tom] Oh nice.
(men grunting)
(robots making mimicking
slurping and groaning)
- [Crow] Let me just tuck your
intestines back in here, heh.
- [Tom] And there on his colon was a hook.
- [Joel] Well, let's
see, I see Van Morrison,
I see Meatloaf, and Spock.
- [Tom] So long, chum! (laughing)
- [Joel] He refrigerates his bowling bag?
- [Crow] Ah, this one's better.
- [Tom] Out in a minute, Mitchell!
Taking a shower!
- [Crow] Either those curtains go or I do.
- [Joel] Dead calm.
- [Crow] Dead clam.
- [Tom] Boy, this sure is good booze!
Captain Schlitz, I think your order's up!
- Benton?
- [Joel] Harbor, Michigan.
(Tom singing "Jaws" theme)
- [Joel] Ah, I'll make sandwiches.
- [Crow] You'll never
take me alive, coppers.
- Hey Mitchell!
- [Tom] Yeah?
Oh, damn.
- That's very impressive!
Very smart, Mitchell, very tough.
You know that you and me have
over a million dollars here?
You know what I'm saying?
Over a million dollars
right here in a bag.
You don't have to be a pig
for the rest of your life, Mitchell.
- [Crow] Well, I kinda do!
- Hey Mitchell, you're smart
enough for something better.
- [Tom] Oh, you're smart enough Mitchell.
- Take a look at it!
- [Tom] You're gonna like it! (laughing)
Let's rip off the last scene
from "Key Largo," Mitchell!
- I'm throwing it out!
- [Crow] Grab anything
frilly outta there you want!
- Why don't we talk
about about it, Mitchell?
Here's my gun.
No reason to fight.
We're smart, we'll both be okay.
- [Joel] Okay, I'm gonna
start taking off my clothes,
you better stop me!
- [Tom] Counselor!
(gunfire)
- [Crow] So the deal's off then?
- [Joel] I think it was
one of those effects
too expensive to show.
- [Tom] I’ll never grow
old, I’ll never die,
and I’ll always eat oatmeal.
- [Crow] Mr. Roper? You home?
- [Joel] Mitchell, license to slouch.
- [Tom] Hmm.
You know it's about this
time with any killing spree
that you really oughta turn
the gun on yourself, you know?
- [Crow] Yeah.
Turn it.
- [Robots] Turn it, turn it!
- [Joel] Guys, come on.
- [Tom] Do the deed, do it.
- [Joel] Hm?
Huh.
- [Tom] My my my my apartment.
- [Crow] I'd knock, but
I know I'm not home.
- [Joel] I love pulling
my gun when I go in
my own apartment, scares
my cats half to death.
- [Tom] Well, no one's
disturbed his porn pile.
- Out!
- [Tom] Huh?
- [Mitchell] Look at me!
(Mitchell and Greta yelling)
On your knees.
- [Tom] Oh.
(Mitchell yelling)
- [Crow] Yanni, you're home!
- [Joel] Okay clothes,
hold it right there.
- [Tom] That was close.
- [Crow] Alright, John
Tesh, I know you’re in here.
- [Tom] Alright kitchen, freeze!
- [Joel And Robots] Surprise!
♫ Happy birthday to you ♫
- [Tom] Not a thought in her head.
There.
- [Joel] So, how was your day?
- You get a kick out
of this kind of thing?
- [Tom] It has its moments.
- [Mitchell] How'd you get in here?
- Through the door.
- It was locked.
- [Tom] She's got a key.
- Can I put my hands down now?
- What the heck, the kitchen!
- I had to eat!
- [Crow] What, did you have
Mickey Rourke over or something?
- [Mitchell] Well, you could
at least wash the dishes.
- There's no machine.
- Where I come from you
wash them in the sink
and dry it with a cloth,
try it before you leave.
- [Joel] Yeah, well where you
come from, beer's an entree.
- [Greta] Hey!
(Tom talking quickly)
- [Joel] Man, he's only
got a couple more minutes
left to be likable, you
think he can pull it off?
- [Crow] I doubt it.
- [Tom] Hey, that shower wasn't bad.
I've been afraid of it all these years.
- [Joel] Wait a minute,
would you stop that?
(Joel and robots groaning)
- [Crow] I can't imagine why
Mitchell Two never came out.
(laughing)
- [Joel] Mitchell, honey?
Time to get ready for school.
- Mitchell?
(Mitchell grumbling)
Can I come in with you?
(Mitchell groaning)
- [Tom] Chair over there
folds out into a single.
- What do you want to
sleep with me for, huh?
- [Crow] Yeah?
- Nobody paying you this time.
- [Tom] I'm doing it on spec.
- [Crow] (sniffing) Do I smell pachyderms?
- [Greta] What's the matter?
- [Tom] Do you work with an orangutan?
- Grass.
Yep, that's grass.
- [Joel] Oh, no wonder she's
attracted to him, she's stoned.
- [Crow] Ah.
- [Mitchell] Oh boy.
- [Crow] Where's your
Cheech and Chong album?
- [Tom] You got any Froot Loops?
- [Crow] God, I love him.
- Uh huh, oh yeah.
Mm hmm.
(Crow grunting)
Alright, let's get your coat.
- [Joel] Oh, zero tolerance is so funny!
(smarmy music)
- [Tom] It's our Mitchell! (laughing)
♫ My my my my Mitchell
(robots clicking tongues)
♫ What would your mama say ♫
- [Crow] She'd say he's not
mine, you can't prove it!
Yeah.
(man singing)
- [Joel] Oh, he sounds funny, doesn't he?
♫ Put 'em on your feet
give your dogs a treat
♫ What a comfortable shoe ♫
- [Crow] The hood to the
Mustang got a credit!
(smarmy music)
- [Tom] Oh Hoyt, how could you?
- [Joel] Hoyt, what happened?
- [Tom] Nitrous.
- [Crow] You know Joe Don Baker would be
perfect for "Elvis: The Dying Days."
(laughing)
(clicking in beat to song)
- [Tom] Oh, it's just
stream of consciousness,
he stopped singing about
Mitchell about five minutes ago.
(laughing)
(singing)
- [Joel] Mitchell!
- 20 seconds to expulsion!
- Okay, alright, we've
got this letter to read.
Let's put it it upon still store.
Okay, this comes to us from a wo--
- 10 seconds and counting!
10, nine, eight--
- Gypsy, could you please turn
off these emergency lights?
We got this letter to read!
- Sure!
One! Expulsion!
- What the hell was that?
- Yeah, where's Joel?
- Yeah!
- I can explain everything.
Cambot quick, give me rocket number nine!
He'll finally get to be
among his own in the wild.
- [Crow] Hey look, there's a prize inside
that box of Hamdingers!
An escape pod!
- Hey guys, look at me,
I'm on my way to Earth,
pretty crazy, huh?
- [Crow] What about us?
- [Tom] Yeah!
- [Crow] What are we supposed
to do without you?
Who's gonna teach us about what
it is to be human and stuff?
- Yeah!
- Listen you guys, at this point,
you guys know as much about it as I do.
Listen, you know, I
don't have a lot of time,
my signal's starting to break up,
I can tell I'm getting out of range.
Listen, if you look under
the desk there's a plaque
I made for you guys to
put up to remember me by!
- Yeah, here it is, look.
Boy, nice job, Joel, very
professional looking.
Really, nice job.
- Yeah, thanks.
I really gotta get out of
here, I'm almost out of range.
Listen you guys, be strong
and true, I love you, bye!
- Huh, it's been a big day.
Who's hungry?
- No, not yet doofus, let's
find out what's on the plaque!
- Oh, okay.
- Press that button there.
- Oh yeah.
- A recording.
- [Joel] To all on the
Satellite of Love from Joel.
- Hey that's us!
- [Crow and Tom] Shh!
- [Joel] The whole world is a circus
if you look at it the right way.
Every time you pick up a handful of dust,
you see not the dust,
but a mystery, a marvel,
there in your hand.
Every time you stop and think,
"I'm alive, and being alive is fantastic."
Every time such a thing happens,
you are part of the circus of Dr. Lao.
- What?
- [Crow] What?
- "Circus of Dr. Lao?"
Oh gee, brother.
Joel leaves and his last words
are from a George Pal movie?
I thought it would be something profound!
You know, like from the Psalms,
or the Upanishads or even the
Desiderata for that matter!
- [Voiceover] Last transmission from Joel
coming in on Hexfield.
- Joel, buddy!
"Circus of Dr. Lao?"
I don't get it!
- Hey, it's my favorite movie, so sue me!
I got to go, guys.
Hey, see you later!
Sorry, folks, I can't come back!
I don't know how it works!
Goodbye!
- Bye!
- Wow.
- Oh, I'm going to miss him.
- Well, I guess he's
gone for good, fellas.
That only means one thing.
I'm in charge.
- Well, race you to the Mallowcups.
I found out where he hides them.
- Oh, Crow, too soon!
- Think they'll send us a new guy?
- Oh sure, they're bound to.
But, until that happens,
panic!
(robots yelling)
- Panic!
- Oh, Joel!
No, no, no!
(robots yelling)
What are we gonna do,
what are we gonna do?
(robots yelling)
- Nothing like a good shower
to make one feel new again, huh?
I feel great!
Nothing can get in the
way of my good mood.
Whats goin' on, Frank?
- Oh, not much.
Inventory's under control,
floor needs mopping,
Joel escaped from the Satellite of Love.
- Well, I see you have
the situation well in ha--
What?
Joel escaped from the Satellite of Love?
- I better get started on that floor.
- Frank!
My towel and your hind
have an appointment.
But first we've got to rescue Joel.
Oh no, no, Frank!
He's landed safely in
the Australian outback!
- Well, let's just hope he
landed on Yahoo Serious.
- Well, that's a good
point Frank, because.
Frank!
Can't you see we're ruined?
What are we gonna do?
- Well, we could send
someone else into space.
- Who are we gonna find at this late date
to send into space?
- Could you guys sign my time card?
(laughing)
(evil laughing)
- Are you thinking what
I'm thinking, Frank?
- Yeah, you're not gonna
sign his time card are you?
- Come on, you gotta sign my time card.
- Of course I'll sign
your time card, young man!
In fact, I think you're
going to be working for me
for a long, long time.
Push the button, Frank.
Say Mike, what size jumpsuit do you wear?
(Mike groaning)
("Love Theme from MST3K" instrumental)
- You're lying through your teeth!
- [Mitchell] Buzz off, huh?
- Buzz off!
- [Mitchell] Buzz off, kid!